{
    "id": "a576f94295da488e88c9f3d3bd6499ff",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Arthritis is a common complaint ……………………….. the elderly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "between",
                "among"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "284ed76635c0404884b5f75e399d820f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did she confide her plans …………………………. you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "030c69b6d6cc4e5097792ede48d9fac0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Diplomas were conferred ………………………… members of the graduating class.",
            "description": "confer + on",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "95136ce92a214ed4b815b2d5b8bc2a09"
        },
        {
            "question": "The bank manager has complete confidence ……………………….. the tellers.",
            "description": "confidence + in",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "346a1d5b977b48938bb33e07e25e0525"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please confine your remarks …………………………. the topic under discussion.",
            "description": "confine + to",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3d0f3b5073254629999d490dfa0b7b55"
        },
        {
            "question": "I congratulate you ……………………………. your twentieth anniversary.",
            "description": "congratulate + on",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6960fef8d6e14f179710ce4d3b2b4b85"
        },
        {
            "question": "You confused me …………………………… my twin brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc12af15c0d54d02881681b42a45ffd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Were you conscious …………………………… his hostility?",
            "description": "conscious + of",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "add3d73652c9466a9494657da652446c"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a bitter contest ………………………….. wills.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "among",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59f34437a4434248be657e152e562e73"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must be prepared …………………………… any contingency.",
            "description": "prepared + for",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "71585a49a03546488aae5a582b573e4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Whether the picnic is held or not is dependent ………………………….. the weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ca5ccf394e3640988b8ccbf8fa2c93fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lying is contrary …………………………….. my beliefs.",
            "description": "contrary + to",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26a78f8ce2d0424ea3b99906878ca61e"
        }
    ]
}